Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 42, folder: 18 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Item 26: Agreement between Telephone Workers Union Of New Jersey and New Jersey Bell Telephone Company, Publication (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Item 27: Agreement between Commercial Telephone Workers Of New Jersey and New Jersey Bell Telephone Company, Publication (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Item 28: Agreement between Telephone Workers Union Of New Jersey and New Jersey Bell Telephone Company, Publication (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Box: 42, folder: 19 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Faculty and Staff Handbook Section Two, Publication (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Faculty and Staff Handbook Section Three, Publication (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Personnel Policies and Procedures, Publication (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Box: 42, folder: 20 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Welcome to New Jersey Bell, Publication (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Your Job Your Company & You, Publication (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Box: 42, folder: 21 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: New Jersey State Employees' Awards Program, Publication (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Rules and Regulations and Statement of Procedure, Publication (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Box: 42, folder: 22 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Employer Guide to Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Box: 42, folder: 23 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Announce a Course in Administrative Management for Small Manufacturers, Publication (Box 42, Folder 23)
    March 26 - May 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Reference Guide to State and Federal Child Labor Laws, Publication (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: Tax Time Table -- June, 1956, Publication (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: New Jersey Members of the Eighty-Fifth Congress, Publication (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: Payroll Tax Finder, Publication (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Item 6: Payroll Tax Finder, Publication (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Item 7: News Letter, Publication (Box 42, Folder 23)
    June 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: News Letter, Publication (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Item 9: Tax Time Table - December, 1956, Publication (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: Members of New Jersey Manufacturers Association, Publication (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Item 11: Unemployment Compensation Benefits In Labor Disputes, Publication (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Item 12: The Governor's Tax Program NJMA Position And Analysis, Publication (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Box: 42, folder: 24 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Rules and Regulations and Statement of Procedure, Publication (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Proposed Rules and Regulations and Statement of Procedure New Jersey Public Employment Relations Commission, Publication (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Summary Of The Rules Of The Public Employment Relations Board, Publication (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Box: 42, folder: 25 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Ten Amendments Proposed to Chapter 303, Publication (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: N.J. Court Denies PERC'S Jurisdiction Over Bi-State Agencies, Publication (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Provisional Employees Entitled To Fair Hearing, Publication (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Box: 42, folder: 26 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Weyerhaeuser Company Annual Report 1963, Publication (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Annual Report, Publication (Box 42, Folder 26)
    July 1 - June 30. Item is in English.
- Box: 42, folder: 27 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Announces A Public Conference on Open Burning Dumps to be held at The Soldiers And Sailors War Memorial Building, Publication (Box 42, Folder 27)
- Box: 42, folder: 28 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Staff Manual, Publication (Box 42, Folder 28)
- Box: 42, folder: 29 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Inter Change, Publication (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Inter Change, Publication (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Inter Change, Publication (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: Inter Change, Publication (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Inter Change, Publication (Box 42, Folder 29)
- Box: 42, folder: 30 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Certificate Of Superior Craftsmanship, Publication (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: New York Building Congress. Room 1016. Grand Central Terminal, Publication (Box 42, Folder 30)
    October 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Statement on The Selection Of General Contractors And Sub-Contractors, Publication (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: By-Laws, Publication (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: To The Members Of The New York Building Congress, Publication (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: New York Building Congress, Suite 531-2, 101 Park Avenue, Publication (Box 42, Folder 30)
    August 27-28. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Year Book of the New York Building Congress, Publication (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Item 8: Recognition of Craftsmanship, Publication (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Item 9: To the Members of the Building Trades Working on This Building, Publication (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Item 10: Principles Upon Which Trade Agreements Should Be Based, Publication (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Item 11: Information for Owners in Connection with Award of Certificates of Superior Craftsmanship Issues by Committee on Recognition of Craftsmanship of the New York Building Congress, Publication (Box 42, Folder 30)
- Box: 42, folder: 31 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Our Jobs On The Central and what we can do to make them secure, Publication (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Revised Schedule Of Rates Of Pay, Publication (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: Schedule of Wages Rules And Working Conditions for Firemen Helpers ON Electric Locomotives Hostlers And Hostler Helpers, Publication (Box 42, Folder 31)
- Box: 42, folder: 32 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: You Are Central, Publication (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Item 2: Personal Qualifications Inventory, Publication (Box 42, Folder 32)
- Box: 42, folder: 33 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Methods & Procedures Committee, Publication (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: Employment Manual, Publication (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: Ideal Characteristics of the Ideal Supervisor, Publication (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Item 4: Working on the CENTRAL, Publication (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Item 5: Basic Personal History Summary, Publication (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Item 6: New York Central System, Publication (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Item 7: The New York Central Railroad, Publication (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Item 8: Employment Manual, Publication (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Item 9: New York Central System, Publication (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Item 10: "BILL" The NEW Railroader, Publication (Box 42, Folder 33)
- Box: 42, folder: 34 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Railroad Accident Report, Publication (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: Annual Report 1954, Publication (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Item 3: Management Newsletter, Publication (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Item 4: New York Central Railroad Company 1956, Publication (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Item 5: Company Manners The why and how of keeping old friends and gaining new ones, Publication (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Item 6: News Bureau, Publication (Box 42, Folder 34)
- Box: 42, folder: 35 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: The Case for the Penn-Central Merger A Current Summary, Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: Man, mind and material, Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: New York Central Railarod 30 Largest Stockholders (As Of May 1961), Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Item 4: Modern Railroads, Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Item 5: Service: Challenge of the Sixties, Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
    By Alfred E. Perlman. January-February. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The New York Central Railroad Company Organization Chart, Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Item 7: The Roads We Travel, Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Item 8: New York Central Highlight, Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Item 9: The Positive Side Of The Tracks, Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Item 10: Railroading Is A Business, Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
    By Wm. White. June 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Grand Central Terminal, Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Item 12: Making Hay While The Sun Shines, Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
    By L. W. Horning. October 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Road of Progress The Story of the New York Central System, Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Item 14: Charting The Progress of the New York Central System, Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Item 15: Grand Central Terminal, Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
- Box: 43, folder: 1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Executive Order No. 38, Publication (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Local Laws of The City Of New York For The Year 1967, Publication (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Box: 43, folder: 2 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Central System Road To The Future, Publication (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Box: 43, folder: 3 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: At Your Service, Publication (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: An Action Program For The Aged In New York City, Publication (Box 43, Folder 3)
    By Mayor Robert F. Wagner. November. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Sus Ordeners, Publication (Box 43, Folder 3)
    June 15. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: the O'Dwyer Plan for Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Box: 43, folder: 4 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Third Annual Meeting Of New York City Anti-Crime Committee, Publication (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Annual Report For The Year 1955, Publication (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Annual Report For The Year 1952, Publication (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Box: 43, folder: 5 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Rules And Regulations For Administrative Employees, Publication (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Box: 43, folder: 6 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Amendment To Memorandum Of Understanding between Board Of Transportation and Various Labor Organizations Representing Its Employees, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Board Of Transportation Of The City Of New York, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
    November 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Memorandum Of Understanding between Board Of Transportation and Various Labor Organizations Representing Its Employees, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Amendment To Memorandum Of Understanding between Board Of Transportation and Various Labor Organizations Representing Its Employees, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Agreement between New York City Transit Authority and Amalgamated Transit Union AFL-CIO, Division 726, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Agreement between New York City Transit Authority and Queens Supervisory Association, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Agreement between New York City Transity Authority And Subway Supervisors Association, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Box: 43, folder: 7 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Rules and Regullations Governing Employees Engaged in Operation of the New York City Transit System, Publication (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Box: 43, folder: 8 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Medical Assistance For The Aged, Publication (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: The Civil Rights Act Implications For Business A Forum Discussion At The New York Chamber Of Commerce, November 19 1964, Publication (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Urgently Needed-Amendment Of The Condon-Wadlin Law, Publication (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: A Report: The PATH TO Progress In Commuter Transportation, Publication (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Box: 43, folder: 9 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Bank Job Interviews Set For South Jamaica Center, Publication (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Box: 43, folder: 10 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Open Hearings on "Women's Role In Contemporary American Society", Publication (Box 43, Folder 10)
    September 21-25. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Commission On Human Rights, Publication (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Puerto Rican Workshop, Publication (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: For Your Information, Publication (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Box: 43, folder: 11 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Working for an Open City, Publication (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Box: 43, folder: 12 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Statement Of Mayor Robert F. Wagner Before The Joint Legislative Committee On Industrial And Labor Conditions, Publication (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Box: 43, folder: 13 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Directory of Civil Service Unions and City Employee Organizations, Publication (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Box: 43, folder: 14 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Newsletter, Publication (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Newsletter, Publication (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Box: 43, folder: 15 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Become A Patrolman, Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Employment With The City Of New York, Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Positions For Which Little Education Or Experience Is Required, Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: The Probationary Period A Guide For Supervisors, Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Careers With New York City Government, Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: 1967 Annual Report, Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Report Of The Evaluation Study Of The Municipal Cooperative Education And Work Program, Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
    By Martin Hamburger. April 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: talking disciplinary action A Manual For Supervisors, Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Employee Relations Program, Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Box: 43, folder: 16 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: 1950 And 1951 Port Progress Report, Publication (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Box: 43, folder: 17 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: 75th Anniversary Civil Service, Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: supervision, Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: 1963 annual report, Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: The Personnel Council Of The City Of New York Annual Report 1963-1964, Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Box: 43, folder: 18 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Guide For Supervisors The City's Grievance Procedure, Publication (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Box: 43, folder: 19 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Municipal Civil Service Commission, Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Personnel Administration In The Government Of New York City, Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
    By Wallace S. Sayre, Herbert Kaufman. March. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Analysis By The Municipal Civil Service Commission of the report by Richardson, Bellows, Henry & Co., Inc., Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Rules Of The City Civil Service Commission Of The City Of New York, Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Box: 43, folder: 20 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Office Of Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Box: 43, folder: 21 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Executive Order No. 52 "The Conduct of Labor Relations between The City of New York and its Employees", Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Executive Order No. 52 "The Conduct of Labor Relations between The City of New York and its Employees", Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: The Office Of Collective Bargaining: A New Concept, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Box: 43, folder: 22 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Probationary Report, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Departmental Evaluation of Appointee and Promotee Services, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Clerical-Administrative Occupational Group, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Civil Engineer, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Accountant, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: Bus Operator, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 7: Assistant Train Dispatcher, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Box: 43, folder: 23 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Training Programs, Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Constitution And By-Laws Of The Subway Supervisors Association Of New York City Transit Authority, Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Box: 43, folder: 24 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Board of Higher Education of the City of New York and The Legislative Conference, Publication (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Box: 43, folder: 25 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: New York City Welfare Strike, Publication (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: New York City Welfare Strike, Publication (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Box: 43, folder: 26 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Employee's Handbook, Publication (Box 43, Folder 26)
- Box: 43, folder: 27 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Agreement between The State of New York and The Senate Professional Association, Publication (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Executive Order, Publication (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Box: 43, folder: 28 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 5: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 6: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 7: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 8: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 9: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 10: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 11: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 12: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 13: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 14: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 15: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 16: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 17: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 18: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 19: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 20: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 21: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 22: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 23: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 24: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 25: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 26: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 27: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 28: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 29: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 30: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 31: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 32: New Jersey Public Employer-Employee Relations, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 33: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 34: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 35: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 36: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 37: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 38: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 39: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 40: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 41: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 42: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 43: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 44: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 45: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 46: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 47: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 48: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 49: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 50: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 51: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 52: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 53: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 54: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 55: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 56: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 57: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 58: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 59: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 60: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 61: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 62: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 63: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 64: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 65: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 66: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 67: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 68: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 69: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 70: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 71: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 72: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 73: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 74: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 75: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 76: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 77: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 78: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 79: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 80: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 81: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 82: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 83: nypome Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 84: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 85: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 86: Current Division Publications By Subject, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 87: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 88: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 89: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 90: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 91: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 92: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 93: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 94: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 95: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 96: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 97: The Personnel Club of New York-Dinner Reservation, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 98: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 99: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 100: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 101: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 102: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 103: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 104: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 105: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 106: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 107: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 108: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 109: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 110: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 111: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 112: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 113: nypoma Bulletin, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)